Jackson Hardee 910-685-3007, jphardee@gmail.com

I am a Software Developer with large-scale, geospatial data and web services experience. I have practiced six years of developing and collaborating on software products and platforms, and I shall bring emphasis on teamwork and growth to Cesium.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Bachelors in Computer Science

• GIS Minor, Transfer United, U.S. Presidential Scholar Semifinalist (2017-2021)

SKILLS

Java, Python, SQLite, PostgreSQL, PostGIS, Groovy, JUnit, Airflow, Docker, Kubernetes, AWS(Lambda, S3), JavaScript/TypeScript, Gitlab, Ubuntu/Linux

EXPERIENCE

Mapping Software Engineer

Sept 2021 - Aug 2023

DEKA Research & Development, Manchester NH

- Contributed to domain mapping system comprised of a GIS database, RESTful APIs, an integrated QGIS application, and a pointcloud processing pipeline.
- Oversaw data curation and processing of 100+ sq. miles of urban and residential terrain and engineered massive 3D-GIS renders for demos and field testing.
- On a team of 5 engineers, we developed a client-facing full stack web application for user access control and command-and-control of a robotics system. Solution integrates real-time communication channels and micro-services leveraging container orchestration and cloud infrastructure.

Customer Success Intern

Jun 2019 - Sept 2019

nCino inc., Wilmington, NC

- Professional experience mentored by a variety of employees from customer success, marketing, & product development, learning how nCino & Sales force is implemented.
- I assisting in delivering solutions for five separate customers, writing tests, automating client forms, and use case testing, and writing SOSL/SOQL, Apex, and Visualforce logic.

IT Intern Jan 2014 - Jun 2016

Hardee Hunt & Williams, Wrightsville Beach, NC

• A CTE Internship managing client database and use graphic design softwares and tools to publish and market flyers, postcards, and more.

PROJECTS Tide-Pool

2024

• WIP app showcasing GMRT, a compilation of edited multibeam sonar data,

UNC-CH Education and Involvement

2020-2021

- Developed multiple Android apps using Java and Tensorflow Lite.
- Developed a Neural Network playground on a team of engineers.
- Contributed to Frankin AR art gallery mobile web application.

PERSONAL

I have a Pug, I go golfing, paddleboarding, & I often learn new recipes in the kitchen.